Guide to the International Brotherhood of Teamsters Library Local Union Vertical File Records, 1933-1993 IBT0054
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
IBT Library Local Union Vertical File Records
1933-1993
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America
IBT0054
3 Linear Feet
This collection consists of newspaper clippings, pamphlets, and booklets pertaining to the history of International Brotherhood of Teamsters Local Unions 137-399. The articles range in date from 1933-1993. These were obtained from the Teamsters Library.
Scope and Contents
This collection consists of newspaper clippings, pamphlets, and booklets pertaining to the history and activities of Teamster Local Unions 137-399. The articles range in date from 1933-1993. Most, however, are from the 1980s. There are many notable Unions mentioned in this collection. One referred to is Local 299, which once had James R. Hoffa and Frank Fitzsimmons as Officers. Both men would later serve as General President of the International Brotherhood of Teamsters. Many of the records concern the Local Unions association with organized crime.
Biographical
This collection was obtained from the International Brotherhood of Teamsters Library. Beginning in the 1970s, Local Unions throughout the United States were asked to submit documents relating to their activities. These were stored at Teamster headquarters in Washington, DC. In 2014, the records were transferred to The George Washington University were they remain today.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged numerically by Local Union number.
Access
This collection is open for research.
Labor unions -- United States -- History -- 20th century; Labor
- Local 1714 Records, 1988-1991; Series 1
  - Arbitration Recommendation Re: Joseph E. Harris, 1990 October 16; IBT0054 Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Assault on Staff, 1990; IBT0054 Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - [Bound Grievance File, 1992; IBT0054 Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Carrie Nobles' Grievance, 1990, 1992; IBT0054 Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Council Budget Submission - Personal Infromation FY93, 1992; IBT0054 Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - DCDC Labor Committee News, 15 March 1992; IBT0054 Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Denial of Access into the Maximum Security Facility, 3 November 1987; IBT0054 Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - District of Columbia Department of Corrections Public Employee Relations Board, 18 May 1990; IBT0054 Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Employee Wage and Expense Record, 1991; IBT0054 Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Grievance File no. 030188-01, 1988; IBT0054 Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Grievance Form 12-28-90-01, 1990; IBT0054 Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Grievance Form 110590-01, 1990; IBT0054 Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Grievance Form - Gregory Hanna, 1990; IBT0054 Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Grievance Number 012290-01, 1990; IBT0054 Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Grievance No. 022688, 1988; IBT0054 Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Miscellaneous Local Union Files, Series 3
  - Union de Tronquistas Invencible - 50 anos de dignidad y compromiso Local 901 - from Carlos Marrero, August 2007; IBT0054 Series 3 (Box Shared Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Memoria de boricuas peregrinos Teamsters Local 237 Oral History Project, 12 March 2019; IBT0054 Series 3 (Box Shared Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Local Union 331 Newsletter and Photos, Fall, 2019; IBT0054 Series 3 (Box SHARED Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Local Union 137, 1981-1982; IBT0054 Series 3 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Local Union 138, 1981-1982; IBT0054 Series 3 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Local Union 142, 1981-1982; IBT0054 Series 3 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Local Union 143, 1981; IBT0054 Series 3 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Local Union 144, 1981-1982; IBT0054 Series 3 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Local Union 145, 1985-1986, 1990; IBT0054 Series 3 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Local Union 146, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Local Union 147, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Local Union 148, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Local Union 150, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Local Union 152, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Local Union 153, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Local Union 156, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Local Union 157, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Local Union 158, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Local Union 159, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Local Union 160, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Local Union 162, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Local Union 164, 1981-1982, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Local Union 165, 1979, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Local Union 169, 1982, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Local Union 170, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Local Union 171, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Local Union 174, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Local Union 175, 1956, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Local Union 177, 1981-1982, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Local Union 182, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Local Union 186, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Local Union 190, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Local Union 191, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Local Union 193, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Local Union 196, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Local Union 199, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Local Union 200, 1973, 1981-1982, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Local Union 202, 1981-1983 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Local Union 204, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Local Union 205, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Local Union 208, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Local Union 209, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Local Union 214, 1977-1978, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Local Union 215, 1980-1982 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Local Union 216, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Local Union 217, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Local Union 218, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Local Union 221, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Local Union 223, 1973, 1977-1979, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Local Union 229, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Local Union 233, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Local Union 235, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Local Union 236, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Local Union 237, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Local Union 238, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Local Union 243, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Local Union 244, 1977, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Local Union 245, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Local Union 247, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Local Union 249, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Local Union 250, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Local Union 251, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Local Union 252, 1978, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Local Union 253, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Local Union 255, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Local Union 256, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Local Union 258, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Local Union 259, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Local Union 261, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Local Union 263, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Local Union 264, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Local Union 270, 1978-1979, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Local Union 271, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Local Union 273, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Local Union 274, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Local Union 277, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Local Union 279, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Local Union 281, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Local Union 282, 1977-1978, 1981-1982, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Local Union 283, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Local Union 284, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Local Union 286, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Local Union 287, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Local Union 289, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Local Union 291, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Local Union 293, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Local Union 294, 1981-1983, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Local Union 295, 1981-1982, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Local Union 296, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Local Union 298, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Local Union 299, 1933, 1941, 1969, 1977-1979, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Local Union 303, 1982, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Local Union 305, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Local Union 307, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Local Union 310, 1977, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Local Union 311, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Local Union 313, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Local Union 315, 1978, 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Local Union 317, 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Local Union 320, 1980-1983 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Local Union 324, 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Local Union 337, 1967, 1977, 1981-1982, 1988, 1991-1993 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Local Union 325, 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Local Union 326, 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Local Union 327, 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Local Union 328, 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Local Union 330, 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Local Union 331, 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Local Union 332, 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Local Union 333, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Local Union 335, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Local Union 336, 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Local Union 340, 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Local Union 344, 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Local Union 345, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Local Union 346, 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Local Union 347, 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Local Union 348, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Local Union 350, 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Local Union 354, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Local Union 357, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Local Union 359, 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Local Union 361, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Local Union 362, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Local Union 363, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Local Union 364, 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Local Union 370, 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Local Union 371, 1981-1983 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Local Union 372, 1981-1983, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Local Union 375, 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Local Union 376, 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Local Union 377, 1977, 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Local Union 378, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Local Union 379, 1981-1982, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Local Union 380, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Local Union 381, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Local Union 383, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Local Union 385, 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Local Union 388, 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Local Union 389, 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Local Union 390, 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Local Union 391, 1978-1979, 1981-1982, 1988, 1990, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Local Union 396, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Local Union 397, 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Local Union 398, 1981-1982; IBT0054 Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Local Union 399, 1981-1982, 1989, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 29)